BHAUTIK GODHANIYA

Mobile: +91 88661 33743 eMail: bhautik.godhaniya@gmail.com

Hi, I'm Bhautik Godhaniya and I like to refer to myself as a "Web Designer". I am a front-end software engineer (currently living in Ahmedabad, Gujarat) who likes to focus on client-side UI Development for all devices using web technologies (HTML,CSS & CSS3, SCSS, JQuery, JavaScript). With a strong technical skill-set, attention to detail, and 4 years of experience.

Work Experience

Sr. Frontend Developer

- MetaTtagg Inc Oct 2023 to Present
- Tech Used Html, Css, Scss, Jquery, Javascript, Wordpress, Next.js

_

HTMLDeveloper

- AIS Technolabs Pvt Ltd May 2023 to Sep 2023
- Tech Used Html, Css, Scss, Jquery, Javascript, Wordpress, React.js

❖ Web Designer

- N-Xpert Solution Pvt Ltd
- Mar 2021 to April 2023
- Tech Used Html, Css, Jquery, Javascript, Wordpress, Codeginator, Vue.js

JR.Software Engineer

- Elinsys Pvt Ltd
- June 2020 to May 2021
- Tech Used Html, Css, Jquery, Javascript, Wordpress

❖ Web Designer

- Qrolic Technologies
- June 2019 to May 2020
- Tech Used Html, Css, Scss, Jquery, Javascript, Wordpress

- ✓ HTML 5
- ✓ CSS 3
- ✓ SCSS
- ✓ Bootstrap
- ✓ Jquery
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ Photoshop
- ✓ Figma
- ✓ Adobe XD
- ✓ Wordpress
- ✓ React (Basic)
- ✓ Vue.js (Basic)
- ✓ Nex.js

Educational Qualification

Master's in Computer Application (MCA)

Institute: N J Sonecha Management And Technical Institute (Veraval)

University: Gujarat Technological University

Year of Completion: 2016

Marks: 7.3 CPI

Bachlar in Computer Application (BCA)

Institute: Shree KM & KK Savjani Collage (Veraval)

University: Saurashtra University

Year of Completion: 2013

Marks: 63 %

Additional Details

• **Gender:** Male

Date of Birth: 17 Jun 1993

• Languages: Gujarati, Hindi, English

• LinkedIn: https://in.linkedin.com/in/bhautik-godhaniya-2947a0101

• Hobbies: Watching Movies &Web Series, Visit new places